https://reggaefestivalguide.com/privacy-policy/

~ Privacy Policy ~
United States Online Privacy Statement Effective Date: February 14, 2013
This Online Privacy Statement describes how RBA Publishing Inc. collects information when you:
access sites or use mobile applications that link to this Statement;
open and respond to our e-mails; or
visit any page online that displays our ads or content.
It does not apply to the collection of information in any way other than as listed above.
All Internet sites have the ability to collect information about you. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of every site you visit. When you fill out an information form on our site such as submitting a festival or business link, you give information directly to us. Also when you pay from the Plug and Pay link on your invoice, you are providing personal information.
Do We Share Your Information?
In keeping with RBA Publishing Inc, we do not share Personal Information with anyone, except as described below.
We may share Personal Information as required or permitted by law:
to report or seek information about your credit, and to report or collect on debts owed;
to comply with legal orders and government requests;
to combat fraud or criminal activity, and to protect the rights of RBA Publishing Inc
with Vendors (who are required to safeguard Personal Information) that help us operate our business;
with your consent.
What Are Your Choices?
You may pay us by check or money order. We do not save information from these forms of payment. We will still communicate with you in connection with servicing your account, fulfilling your request, or administering any promotion or any program in which you may have elected to participate. Materials we send you may still include some offers or promotions.
It may take some time for us to process your request and, consistent with applicable law, could take up to 30 days.
How do we keep your Personal Information safe and secure?
We use reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect your Personal Information. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Please do not send us any Personal Information through unsecured channels, including e-mail or social media sites.
Children under 13
Our sites are not for children under 13 years old. We do not knowingly solicit data online from, or market online to, children under 13. If we knowingly receive a child’s Personal Information, we will delete it from our systems.
Can this Statement change?
We may change this Statement at any time. Changes are effective when we post them on this site.
Questions About this Statement?
If you have questions about this Online Privacy Statement, call 1-775-337-8344
Glossary
RBA Publishing Inc is the parent company of these brands: Blues Festival Guide, Blues Festival e-Guide, Reggae Festival Guide, Reggae eGuide, Reggae Guide for iPhone.
MENU
Home
Jukebox
News
Music
Festival Calendar
Upcoming Festivals
2020 Festivals
